[{"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "If they had gone behind Congress' back as you claimed, do you think you can get this overturned legally?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that to assume that the United States of America would use a drone and a hellfire missile to attack someone sitting in a cafe -- look, this goes back to our previous conversation.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Oh, listen, Newt and I have been friends for many, many years.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Do you have any message for Newt Gingrich?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think maybe we need a congressional hearing on the whole issue of what is a danger to the entire flight and what we should -- I think we need to call witnesses since they have made this policy change.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I'm great.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "This looks a fun gig, the movie.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I'm sure.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Is he feeling the heat now, you think?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "You know, I have to say that we have to get a little less sensitive, you know, with the comedians.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Were Amy Poehler and Tina Fey a little unfair to her, did you think, at the Golden Globes with their jibe about her young boyfriends?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I think we really are.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "That's the point you're making, is everyone getting a little thin-skinned here?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I think absolutely.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Is it an important thing to have, you think, to affirm to the world that women matter?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's really hard to work from home.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "What is your view about women working from home, in particular, women?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I started to, but it didn't really work out.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Tell me about that?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Yes, he's the director of the movie and, you know, he is sharing in all of the responsibilities and, in fact, takes on most of the responsibilities where men have such a difficult time being the man behind the woman, he's actually such a great example of someone who is comfortable in that position and you know fills the slots where he has to so that I can go off and do my work.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "He directs this movie, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Get out of here.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "So you know what?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You know, in doing it -- and you feel it -- the impact didn't, you know, work on me, there's no question about it.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "When you look back and when you finished it, what did you think about the career you've had?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "You know, it was totally by luck that I had gotten into music.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "It's about the love of music for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "No, you're not wrong.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Am I wrong?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "AVIS: I've not been surprised, honestly.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "And have you been surprised by them?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I've been married twice.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Would you like to get married to a man one day?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm very pleased.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "But are you -- are you pleased to see the way the gay marriage debate has gone?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Look, well, as far as Kelly is concerned -- and I've been talking about that -- we had a different judgment as to how she reacted to two songs that I gave her that become huge hits, \"Since You've Been Gone,\" and \"Behind These Hazel Eyes,\" as well, you know, as \"Break Away\" and others.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What did you feel about that?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "This is a dispute.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Have you spoken to her since?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "\"Bridge Over Troubled Water\" with Simon & Garfunkel.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What would the single be?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "And, finally, which artist would you take?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, let me -- I would point to Alicia Keys, who, with Pager Edge (ph), I discovered, a Renaissance young woman who writes her own materials, stunning to look at, a major talent within the industry.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "If you could have one to sing to you for the rest of your life, just you and them on a desert island?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Well, I -- yes, you're right.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "And how would you change it?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Have you seen the movie \"Zero Dark Thirty\" yet?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "What I have heard about it, it's a good movie, all right.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "From what you have heard of it, what is -- what is your opinion?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I feel, yes, they have never been that bad, and I think in my time, the relations were good, although we were facing the same threat, and we were dealing with the threat in our own ways.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What is the quickest and best way to fix that international relationship between Pakistan and the United States?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, use of drones, there are two uses of drones.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What is your view of the use of drones generally?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Do you want to take any of the babies?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130308pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Isn't that beautiful?", "qSentId": 585}]